http://www.hi-levelmezzanines.co.uk/privacy-policy

01730 237 190   |   sales@hi-level.co.uk
HomeAbout UsAbout UsRaising the StandardTestimonialsIndustry SectorsIndustry SectorsRetailOfficeWarehousingAutomationProduction & ManufacturingTransportTechnicalOverview – The ProcessDesigniQD PortalBuilding RegulationsQuality StandardsInstallationBudget CalculatorProductsOur ProductsMezzanine FloorsFlooring RangeHandrailsStaircasesPallet GatesFire ProtectionFit-OutOur WorkNewsNewsEventsFeaturesContact UsContactCareersTrade Area
Privacy PolicyHome » Privacy PolicyConsent & Use of Personal InformationWe collect, keep and process your personal information for legitimate business purposes only which may include your name, e-mail address, telephone number, company name and contact address. The legal basis for the collection and processing of this data is for the provision of services by Hi-Level Mezzanines Ltd.By completing our web forms, communicating with us via our social media channels or contacting us by email or phone, you consent to the collection and use of this personal information outlined above.Should we decide to change our Privacy Policy in any way, we will post such changes to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, our use of it and the circumstances under which we would disclose it.How we use your personal data We use your personal information in order to communicate with you and deliver the services requested by you. This may include occasionally notifying you about new services and products we think you might appreciate. We may also use your personal information internally for marketing purposes.We use a third party provider, HubSpot, to email news and updates to subscribers. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see HubSpot’s privacy notice.You can click on ‘manage your preferences’ or ‘unsubscribe’ at any time which are found at the bottom of these emails. Alternatively please contact sales@hi-level.co.uk.Third PartiesWe value your privacy and understand that you don’t want your name, personal details and preferences sold to third parties. Hi-Level Mezzanines Ltd will not sell, trade or rent any form of your information to a third party.CookiesHi-Level’s website uses cookies to allow Google Analytics to function correctly. Cookies do not harm your computer. Cookies collect information about how visitors use our site, e.g. which pages visitors go to most often and if they get error messages from pages. They do not collect information that identifies visitors. All information collected is aggregated (and therefore anonymous) and only used to improve how our website works. By using our website you agree that we can place these type of cookies on your device.Access To Your Personal Information You are entitled to view, amend, or delete your personal information that we hold. Email your request to sales@hi-level.co.uk.You can update your subscription preferences or unsubscribe from our email communications at any time by following the link in the footer of the last email you received from us (“Manage preferences” or “Unsubscribe”) or by sending your request to sales@hi-level.co.uk.Questions & FeedbackIf you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy please e-mail us at sales@hi-level.co.uk.Hi-Level Mezzanines Ltd is the Data Controller in respect of any personal data that you submit to us or that we collect from or about you. We are a limited company registered in England and Wales (registered no. 2595852) with registered offices at Unit 6, Petersfield Business Park, Bedford Road, Petersfield, Hampshire, GU32 3QA.This policy was last updated 20/11/19How can we help?
Budget calculator
Quote request
Contact us
Connect with usMore information
Our Work
Features
Brochures/Datasheets
FAQs
Budget CalculatorReceive a competitive price using our precise budget generator Budget calculator Quote RequestReceive a detailed quote from our estimators Request a quoteWhat our clients say“Hi-Level worked with Tesco on a Clothing Project and installed two 8100sqm mezzanine floors. Hi-Level delivered a smooth installation programme on time, within the agreed budget and to a very high standards.TescoProject Manager“Our project ran smoothly and delivered us a showroom we are proud of. We are very pleased with the results”. Read about the project hereAbsolute MusicSales Director“It’s the first time Tesco have used Hi-Level and I have been very impressed with their approach from start to finish on the project, the product is robust, reliable and has a good quality finish, I would strongly consider using Hi-Level in the future” .Network Development Project Manager, Tesco“Great work, great team, thank you!”Brent Lodge Wildlife Hospital“First rate build quality, prompt friendly service with excellent attention to detail”.Office BuildersDirector“This is the third mezzanine floor we have asked Hi Level to do, the first and second one we had other quotes and both times Hi-Level offered the best deal. Whilst price was a deciding factor, service was too. From original point of contact with Neil through to the design work with Jason, it was excellent. SO very helpful especially with someone like myself with little knowledge on mezzanines, I would highly recommend Hi-Level”.Furniture WorldManaging Director “Very pleased with the attention to detail, a high standard of Health and Safety throughout the project, thanks for delivering a great job”.Stodec LtdContracts Director“The job was completed by Hi-Level very efficiently and in a professional manner”.Guildprime Specialist Contracts“Great service from Hi-Level. A small but critical install in a Prison meant we had restricted installation window. Project was finished early, as no time was wasted adjusting. 5 Stars!”BTSSales Manager “Hi-Level have provided Davies Turner with a perfect solution to our additional floor space requirements delivered on time, on budget and with minimal disruption for such a large mezzanine project in a busy warehouse”.Davies Turner & Co LtdDirector Latest Tweets We're thrilled to announce that we have joined the United Kingdom Warehousing Association (UKWA); a 700+ member net… https://t.co/2uWIqAjLf0 As with most other structures, the installation of a mezzanine floor is governed by Building Regulations. Created t… https://t.co/UKraoY4Jpz Installing a mezzanine floor can be a significant investment. The decision between buying new or second-hand must b… https://t.co/fUosPimy55 As fast delivery becomes a regular expectation, all processes within the supply chain must be optimised. Our latest… https://t.co/evaUZgttmu To celebrate our fantastic product range, we’ve created a short video to highlight them. Follow this link for the f… https://t.co/Lb6y6Z6z5o As the country's workforce gradually returns to offices and warehouses, most businesses are scrutinising their work… https://t.co/aVU4HzWbC7 Like most, Hi-Level have had to make temporary operational changes so that we can continue to quickly and safely de… https://t.co/HdrF0cvyTc Hi-Level Mezzanines Ltd is an experienced partner to retailers looking to maximise their floor space within their c… https://t.co/y0kTyw3yyA For #retail businesses, #mezzaninefloors can be a crucial element of any development programme. They transform unus… https://t.co/dpykS2uJTm Did you know we offer concrete composite decking as one of our bespoke mezzanine flooring options? It is a robust s… https://t.co/1mg8PUEtTb Did you know we offer steel kickplates as standard? We include this because it provides a more durable and aestheti… https://t.co/ojsb4fT0Fv Great to see the building coming along! We're looking forward to seeing the completed project https://t.co/YLDmLXceMu Do you have a head for heights? Feel part of the action by visiting the new 1st floor café and viewing area at Rock… https://t.co/IDqF8hgIT8 A pat on the back to our Business Development Manager Malcolm Plum, he always goes the extra mile for his customers… https://t.co/bykrtBJztI Happy New Year from all of us at Hi-Level https://t.co/7myFZB65FD https://t.co/Op2Xw0QIZc On the day of the Hi-Level team Christmas lunch, we held our own Christmas jumper day! This charitable event helps… https://t.co/GjViU1zQ5y Hi-Level worked with @PPAcademyUK as they relocated to a larger premises in Guildford. Our mezzanine will house mul… https://t.co/HmmQNdBqIl We’re always proud when we can over-deliver and in this case install a mezzanine floor earlier than planned for a c… https://t.co/hL4h5Y5rKs If you’re at @IMHX this week we’d love to get your feedback on our new
#mezzanine app, come on over! https://t.co/ahNjdwJRSi
FollowLatest News Hi-Level’s New Managing Director – Angus WhitemanRead more > Key Factors to Consider When Designing a Mezzanine FloorRead more > Hi-Level Become the Latest Affiliate Member of the UKWARead more >AddressHead Office Hi-Level Mezzanines Ltd Unit 6, Petersfield Business Park Bedford Road Petersfield Hampshire GU32 3QAGet in touch sales@hi-level.co.uk General enquiries: 01730 233223 Sales enquiries: 01730 237190 Fax:
01730 231311Mailing list sign upSign up to our mailing list to receive the latest news and info from Hi-Level. Sign up
© 2020 Hi-Level Mezzanines Ltd | Company Reg No. 2595852 | VAT Reg No. 582 7023 39Site by Wizbit | Sitemap | Privacy Policy
